一种老式的计时方法
an old fashioned way of timekeeping
那是在我们全宇宙接受豌豆系统之前了
before we all universally accepted the bean system.
"豌豆系统才正确"
"The bean system is the way."
关于祖先日  我要告诉你们
For Ancestry Day, I'm gonna tell you
祖先日关于祖先日  我要告诉你们
一个关于某天的某个故事祖先日
a particular story about one particular day
卡洛琳公主面对并克服了祖先日
on which Princess Carolyn faced and overcame
特别的逆境祖先日
particular adversity
故事要追溯到2017年祖先日
all the way back in the year 2017.
故事要追溯到2017年
那天如往常一样
The day began like any other.
卡洛琳公主和他男友  拉尔夫住在一起
Princess Carolyn lived with her boyfriend, Ralph.
她怀孕了  也非常高兴
She was pregnant and very happy.
抱歉我不能陪你去看医生了
Sorry I can't go with you to the doctor.
-别担心  我感觉很棒  -今天很关键
- Don't worry about it. I feel great! - Today is crucial.